×ÖÄ»
Ohh.
Mmm.
×ÖÄ»
Hello? - Hey, Mom.
- Jess? - Yeah.
×ÖÄ»
I'm sorry I'm calling so late.
It's OK.
×ÖÄ»
Is everything all right?
Yeah.
×ÖÄ»
Yeah, I'm fine, I just, um...
I don't even know why I called.
×ÖÄ»
I think I'm just overworked and overtired.
Probably from all the travel.
×ÖÄ»
I get it, sweetheart.
You know, I never told you this,
×ÖÄ»
but I had terrible anxiety when I was your age.
Sometimes it was so bad, I mean,
×ÖÄ»
I couldn't even get out of bed and face the day.
I hope that's not happening to you.
×ÖÄ»
Are you... are you sure you're OK?
Yeah, I'm fine, I just...
×ÖÄ»
I keep having this bad dream.
Would you like to talk about it?
×ÖÄ»
Jess? Are you there?
Yeah. Yeah. Um...
×ÖÄ»
I say that because sometimes nightmares are just nightmares.
But sometimes they feel so real
×ÖÄ»
they spill over into the daytime.
You don't want that.
×ÖÄ»
You know, I can come over if you want.
Mom, I'm like five hours away.
×ÖÄ»
So?
So I'm... I'm fine.
×ÖÄ»
I think I just needed to hear a comforting voice.
- I love you. - I love you too, baby.
×ÖÄ»
- Bye, Mom. - Hey, wait.
What?
×ÖÄ»
I'm just getting this...
bad energy from your side of the phone,
×ÖÄ»
like there's something...
lurking around you or something.
×ÖÄ»
Something not quite right.
Something that might be after you, Jess.
×ÖÄ»
Mom, if you're trying to be funny, this is not...
This is no joke!
×ÖÄ»
You could be in real danger, baby!
You need to get yourself out of that place!
×ÖÄ»
Mom, calm down...
Just get out of that motel, Jess!
×ÖÄ»
- Mom! Mom! - Get out of there!
- Right now! - Mom, I'm stuck!
×ÖÄ»
They're right there, Jessie, run!
Mom, I'm stuck!
×ÖÄ»
What is wrong with you? Run!
Mom, help! Mom!
×ÖÄ»
Fuck this.
Fuck! You!
×ÖÄ»
- - What?
Fuck.
×ÖÄ»
No. No.
Fuck!
×ÖÄ»
Mom.
Jesus, you scared the shit out of me.
×ÖÄ»
Sweetie, you called me and I was worried about you.
What are you still doing here? I told you to get out.
×ÖÄ»
Mom, there's no door.
- Of course there is. - Yeah, well,
×ÖÄ»
we can't get out. It... It's locked.
Of course it is.
×ÖÄ»
Why didn't you try the key?
The key?
×ÖÄ»
Yes. Jess, are you OK?
No.
×ÖÄ»
No, wait. The...
The key is how you get in.
×ÖÄ»
You don't open a door from the inside with a key.
What are you talking about, Jess? I've got the key right here.
×ÖÄ»
It was on the table.
Come on. Let's get out of this place.
×ÖÄ»
- - See?
Come on!
×ÖÄ»
Jess, let's go!
Jess.
×ÖÄ»
Mom, look out!
No, plea... Please!
×ÖÄ»
- -
911. What's your emergency?
×ÖÄ»
Hi. I'm... I'm at the motel off the parkway.
Can you please send someone?
×ÖÄ»
What's your emergency?
I think that there's someone... or something... in my room
×ÖÄ»
that's trying to harm me.